thetimes100.co.uk 2008-06-24

# The Times 100 - Edition 12 - Privacy Policy

The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.

 **1\. Statement of intent**

From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address etc.) in order to receive or use services on our website. Such services include newsletters, competitions, downloads and membership. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable The Times 100 and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. The Times 100 will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.

 **2\. Information on visitors**

During the course of any visit to The Times 100, the pages you see, along with something called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. Most, if not all, websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. In this instance a 'temporary cookie' (one that is deleted when you exit your web browser) is used to store your e-mail address when logging in to access/download certain areas of the site.

Cookies are completely optional on The Times 100 and you have to select the 'remember me' option in order to activate them, they are used only to save you having to enter your information each time you wish to access/download certain areas of the site.

 **3\. Use and storage of your personal information**

When you supply any personal information to The Times 100 (e.g. for competitions, or to download certain files) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with that data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular pages that let you know why we are requesting the information). In general, any information you provide to The Times 100 will only be used within the The Times 100 and *MBA Publishing. It will never be supplied to anyone outside these organisations without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it. Also, if you post or send offensive or inappropriate content anywhere on or to The Times 100 or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on The Times 100, and the The Times 100 considers such behaviour to be serious and/or repeated, The Times 100 can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour. This may include informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school or e-mail provider about the content and your behaviour.

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, you no longer wish to continue your registration as a user. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

 **4\. Users 16 and under**

If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to the Times 100. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

*The Times 100 is produced by:

MBA Publishing Ltd  
26 Bridge Street  
Tadcaster  
LS24 9AJ

Copyright ©2006. MBA Publishing Ltd. All Rights Reserved
